PHONE +84 948 935 300 EMAIL hi@auduongtuan.com website/portfolio https://auduongtuan.com

### INTRODUCTION

I'm a software designer and developer who strives to create good-experience digital products. Proudly having many skills that span a spectrum of disciplines, I use them to solve problems in creative, organized, and programmatic ways.

#### CAREER OBJECTIVE

Despite having more experience in design, I'm looking for an engineer-driven role in which I could enhance my technical skills and dig into the product development process. Furthermore, it will be best if I can work in a role like <u>UX Engineer</u> - the dream job that makes use of my programming and design skills.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

BAEMIN Vietnam Oct 2022 - Current

Product designer / Front-end developer, Full-time

- Design Direct Discount feature for Merchant app.
- Conduct plan for new design system (web and mobile).
- Create design system's Figma web UI Kit and implement them based on MUI. Support FE developers applying it to current products.
- Document design system's components in the Storybook site.
- Create <u>BM i18n</u> Internationalization Figma plugin to improve multi-language product development process (Figma API + React, Redux, TailwindCSS, Radix UI)

Aperia Vietnam Apr 2020 - Sep 2022

UI/UX designer / Front-end developer, Full-time

Worked as a designer (60%) and an associate front-end developer (40%) in the Design system team.

- Create and maintain UI kits in Sketch & Figma.
- Document components (UI specs, behaviors, and storybook) and design patterns.
- Prototype <u>complex concepts</u> using HTML/CSS/JS and implement some React components.
- Create Figma plugins to help improve design workflow.

Other works include:

- Implement and maintain company website (using WordPress and Tailwind CSS)
- Create some internal tools such as <u>Email Signature Generator</u>, <u>Sketch Cloud files</u> downloader, ...

### Samsung Vietnam

Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

UI/UX designer, Full-time

Joined in a new Samsung design team in Vietnam to build apps for IOT devices.

**ECOE Vietnam** 

Mar 2019 - Oct 2019

UI/UX designer, Contract

Joined to a design team building a new estate platform in Vietnam Market.

#### Viivue Web Boutique

Nov 2018 - Mar 2019

Web designer, Part-time

Worked as a part-time web designer for an agency (mainly using WordPress as a CMS).

**Yeah1 Network**Graphic designer and Video editor, Part-time

Dec 2017 - Jul 2018

Worked as a part-time designer and video editor to support marketing materials, landing pages, and videos for Phở Đặc Biệt.

### **EDUCATION**

### **University of Science (HCMUS)**

BSc in Information Technology, class of 2021

#### University of Architecture HCMC (UAH)

BFA in Graphic Design, class of 2016

### **Keyframe Training**

Motion graphic & C4D animation, class of 2016

## Luong The Vinh High School For The Gifted

Specialization in Physics, class of 2013

#### **SKILLS & STACK**

#### **Skills**

- Product design
- Design system / DesignOps
- Web development
- Web standards, accessibility best practices
- Motion graphics

### **Design Tools**

- · Figma, Sketch
- Figma plugin development
- Adobe Creative Suite (PTS, AI, AE, Pr)
- Blender and C4D (basic experience)

# **Tech Stack**

- · HTML, CSS
- Javascript, Typescript
- ReactJS, NextJS, jQuery
- · Redux, Zustand
- SCSS, TailwindCSS, styled-components
- MUI, Ant Design, Radix UI, Headless UI
- PHP, WordPress
- React Native (basic experience)
- Swift, Swift UI (basic experience)

#### LANGUAGES

- Vietnamese (Native)
- English (IELTS 7.0)